[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using JavaScript? 1",
        "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "Immediate feedback to the visitors",
            "Increased interactivity",
            "All of the above",
            "Less server interaction"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How can you get the total number of arguments passed to a function ? 2",
        "correctAnswer": "Using arguments.length property",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "None of the above.",
            "Using arguments.length property",
            "Using args.length property",
            "Both of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL 3?",
        "correctAnswer": "link()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "link()",
            "sub()",
            "sup()",
            "small()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value? 4",
        "correctAnswer": "reduce()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "reduceRight()",
            "reduce()",
            "pop()",
            "push()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which of the following function of Array object extracts a section of an array and returns a new array? 5",
        "correctAnswer": "slice()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "slice()",
            "reverse()",
            "shift()",
            "some()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array? 6",
        "correctAnswer": "reverse()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "changeOrder(order)",
            "sort(order)",
            "reverse()",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array? 7",
        "correctAnswer": "forEach()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "loop()",
            "forEach()",
            "while()",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following function of String object splits a String object into an array of strings by separating the string into substrings? 8",
        "correctAnswer": "split()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "split()",
            "slice()",
            "replace()",
            "search()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which of the following function of Number object defines how many total digits to display of a number? 9",
        "correctAnswer": "toPrecision()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "toExponential()",
            "toLocaleString()",
            "toPrecision()",
            "toFixed()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to upper case? 10",
        "correctAnswer": "toUpperCase()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "toLocaleUpperCase()",
            "toUpperCase()",
            "substring()",
            "toString()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which built-in method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array? 11",
        "correctAnswer": "push()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "last()",
            "None of the above.",
            "push()",
            "put()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Which of the following function of Array object returns a new array comprised of this array joined with other array(s) and/or value(s)? 12",
        "correctAnswer": "concat()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "some()",
            "pop()",
            "concat()",
            "push()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Which of the following function of Array object joins all elements of an array into a string?  13",
        "correctAnswer": "join()",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "concat()",
            "join()",
            "pop()",
            "map()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to redirect a url using JavaScript? 14",
        "correctAnswer": "window.location='http://www.newlocation.com'",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "document.location='http://www.newlocation.com'",
            "navigator.location='http://www.newlocation.com'",
            "browser.location='http://www.newlocation.com'",
            "window.location='http://www.newlocation.com'"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript? 15",
        "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
        "answerSuggested": [
            "JavaScript is a lightweight, interpreted programming language",
            "JavaScript is designed for creating network-centric applications",
            "All of the above",
            "JavaScript is complementary to and integrated with Java"
        ]
    }
]